

Seattle, WA

- (907) 750-2617
- aaron.lee.andrews@gmail.com
- aquinsgreatgames.com

Aaron Andrews

Summary

1+ years of professional experience with the Unity Game Engine
1 year of Full-stack Development creating microservices
Looking to make my mark by creating games, software, and tools that customers love using, and that my fellow engineers love working with.
Forever a student and looking for new things to learn.

Experience

Jr Full Stack Developer

HCL America (Client, Boeing)

July 2019 – January 2020

- Full-stack development of web applications and microservices
- Main project was a Kanban Board
 - Users created and logged in with personal accounts
 - Users could create and modify their projects and tasks
- Frontend React, Redux, NodeJs, Javascript
- Backend Hibernate, Spring-boot, MySQL, Java
- Cloud technologies
 - Mostly Cloud Foundry, attained official certification
 - Some AWS and Azure

Unity Programmer November 2018 – July 2019 *PeekaVR*

- Bringing children's books to life in virtual reality
- Programmed interactions with assets in the scenes
 - Coding was done with C# inside Visual Studio
- Built out scenes from the books
 - o Unity game engine
 - Created for VR
 - Used in mobile devices



SKILLS

Game Development

Unity - C#

ReactJs, Redux

Springboot – Java

MySQL

Pivotal Cloud Foundry

NodeJs

Github

Visual Studio

C++

Javascript

Education

Cloud Foundry Certified Developer

Dec 2019

Linux Foundation

Advanced Diploma of Professional Game Development

May 2018

Academy of Interactive Entertainment, Seattle, WA

Bachelors of Science, Computer Science

August 2016

University of Alaska Fairbanks (UAF), Fairbanks, AK

Projects

Game Library Interface

2018 - 2019

- A game library that mimics the one used inside of the SpringboardVR game launcher.
- Desktop application for a VR Arcade to easily show customers what games are offered.
- Written in C# and powered by the Unity game engine.
- Web application currently being developed
 - Unity WebGl frontend
 - o Java, Spring backend
 - o Fetches files from a box.com repository

Personal Website: aquinsgreatgames.com

2016 - 2020

- Hosted on personal server, running Linux
- Originally written in base Javascript and Html
- Rewritten in ReactJs

Multiple Class and Game Jam Projects

2012 - 2020

- Gleeth God
 - o Unity, C#, AI
- Repair Robot
 - o Unity, C#, UI
- Techno Viking
 - o Unreal Engine, Graphical Effects, Blueprints
- Checkers Neural Network
 - o AI, C++
- Dinaki Adventures
 - o C++, QT